<blog-posts>
	<post>
		<heading>Seattle Trip, Part 2</heading>
		<date>March 8, 2016</date>
		<author>Mike</date>
		<image>img/seattle2.jpg</image>
		<image-alt>Hale's Ales brews.</image-alt>
		<text>One of the nights we were in Seattle we were able to get away from Mel's adorable, yet exhausting, nieces and spend the night on our own exploring the Fremont section of the city. While there, were were able to stop at two local breweries - Hale's Ales and Bad Jimmy's.</text>
		<subheading>Hale's Ales</subheading>
		<image>img/hales.jpg</image>
		<image-alt>Hale's Ales</image-alt>
		<text>Hale's Ales is one of the first breweries to pop up in the Fremont area. The two brews we shared - a cream ale and a barrel-aged stout - were quite delicious, as was the bread pudding.</text>
		<subheading>Bad Jimmy's</subheading>
		<image>img/jimmys.jpg</image>
		<image-alt>Flight at Bad Jimmy's.</image-alt>
		<text>Bad Jimmy's Brewing is just a block away from Hale's. A small place situated back off the street, but very welcoming. We got a flight of beers to try, including a Samoa Girl Scout Cookie inspired beer and a habanero amber ale. Their small operation allows them to take chances and experiment with their batches, which I always welcome.
		</text>
	</post>
	<post>
		<heading>Seattle Trip, Part 1</heading>
		<date>March 6, 2016</date>
		<author>Mike</date>
		<image>img/seattle1.jpg</image>
		<image-alt>Pike Brewery flight.</image-alt>
		<text>While Pitt was on spring break, I was also able to get the week off of work so that my girlfriend and I could take a trip out to Seattle to visit her sister and family. Of course, no first trip to Seattle would be complete without exploring the markets at Pike Place.</text>
		<text>After taking in the market and watching the obligatory fish tosses, we stopped in at Pike Brewing for lunch and sampled a flight of their flagship beers (picture above). While none of the brews really blew me away, they were decent enough and the food was tasty. I would be interested in trying some of their seasonal or limited releases when we next find ourselves on the west coast.</text>
	</post>
	<post>
		<heading>Welcome!</heading>
		<date>March 3, 2016</date>
		<author>Mike</date>
		<image>img/glasses.jpg</image>
		<image-alt>My glassware.</image-alt>
		<text>Welcome to my beer blog. I'm Mike, and by the above picture you may have guessed that I enjoy beer, including the glassware that gets it from bottle to lips. Here I hope to chronicle my love of beer through various outings to breweries or just reviewing beers that I've had. Please stay and look around. Enjoy.</text>
	</post>
<blog-posts>